Class of 1957 Records, 1953-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1957 Records
1953-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1957.
RG 80 UUID:85354ec9-8515-4bc7-9286-8d6daa0b7ff8
15 boxes (12.6 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1957.
The Class of 1957 was the seventy-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1957 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1957, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, surveys, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1957 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Fund-Special Gifts Committee 1972-1984 (Box 2205, Folder 1)
- Alumnae Officers undated (Box 2205, Folder 2)
- Calendar of Events 1956-1957 (Box 2205, Folder 3)
- Class Cards and Alumnae Lists 1981 (Box 2205, Folder 4)
- Commencement 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 5)
- Commencement-Music 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 6)
- Commencement-Photographs 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 7)
- Commencement-Speaker 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 8)
- Dinner 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 9)
- Freshman Handbook 1953-1954 (Box 2205, Folder 10)
- Freshman Orientation 1953 (Box 2205, Folder 11)
- Gold Key Guides-Photographs 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 12)
- Groups 1953-1957 (Box 2205, Folder 13)
- History 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 14)
- Hoop Rolling 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 15)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 16)
- Junior Ushers 1956 (Box 2205, Folder 17)
- Class Letters 1966-1984, 2002 (Box 2205, Folder 18)
- Class Letters-Correspondence 1982-1985 (Box 2205, Folder 19)
- Officers 1953-1954 (Box 2205, Folder 20)
- Organization undated (Box 2205, Folder 21)
- Picnics and Luncheons 1967, 1978 (Box 2205, Folder 22)
- Posture Picture Study 1981 (Box 2205, Folder 23)
- Class President's Records 1972-1982 (Box 2205, Folder 24)
- Rally Day 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 25)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 2205, Folder 26)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2205, Folder 27)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 2206, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1977 (Box 2206, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Alumnae Fund 1977 (Box 2206, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 4)
- Reunions-Alumnae Fund Committee 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 5)
- Reunions-Photographs 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 6)
- Reunions-Reunion Book 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 7)
- Reunions-Survey 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2206, Folder 9)
- Reunions-Photographs 1992 (Box 2206, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1997-2002 (Box 2206, Folder 11)
- Secretary 1972 (Box 2206, Folder 12)
- Songs 1955-1957 (Box 2206, Folder 13)
- Sophomore Push 1955 (Box 2206, Folder 14)
- Sophomore Carnival 1955 (Box 2206, Folder 15)
- Treasurer's Records 1972-1984 (Box 2206, Folder 16)
- Who's Who 1953 (Box 2206, Folder 17)
- Scrapbook (Box OV)
- Scrapbook (Box OV)
- Scrapbook (Box OV)
- Scrapbook (Box OV)
- Reunion Photo Album (Box OV)
- Reunion Scrapbook 1980's (Box OV)
- Reunion Scrapbook-30th Reunion 1987 (Box OV)